♪The world keeps changing♪
♪A thousand years pass
in the blink of an eye♪
♪Shoulder to shoulder♪
♪We stand above the world♪
♪Our identities switch♪
♪The world turns upside down♪
♪Watch me♪
♪Stir up a storm♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our blood is boiling♪
♪The genius emperor plots
with brilliant strategy♪
♪The slacker general
is unmatched in battle♪
♪The business world is in turmoil♪
♪The court is rife with intrigue♪
♪We will conquer the world♪
♪There's no escape for the traitors♪
=No Way! My Bro is the Emperor=
=Episode 9=
The traitor General Sun Beiming
raised a private army,
held the imperial consort hostage,
and plotted regicide.
His crimes are unforgivable.
He deserved to die.
Cavalry General Gu Bei
has shown great loyalty and valor.
He is hereby promoted
to Commander of the Imperial Guards,
to defend and protect the capital.
Princess Hulv of the Plains
is permitted to remain in the capital
for her meritorious service.
That's all.
- Wise judgment, Your Majesty.
Your Majesty,
Sun Beiming deserved his fate,
but he was Your Majesty's
appointed prince consort.
As for his marriage
to Princess Xiao Ling...
Sun Beiming abducted the Consort and
tried to force the Princess into marriage.
Naturally, the marriage doesn't count.
I shall find the Princess
a worthy husband.
Gu Bei,
for your meritorious service,
- I'll give you the Princess's hand...
-  No!
I won't allow it.
Outrageous!
How dare you defy His Majesty?
Such blatant disrespect to His Majesty.
As expected, a foreign woman
has treacherous intentions.
Official Li, don't exaggerate the issue.
In my humble opinion,
a progressive nation like Jing
shouldn't cling to arranged marriages.
Marriage
should be a woman's own choice.
Official Gu,
a woman's marriage
has always been decided
by her parents and matchmakers.
Official Hu,
that's an outdated way of thinking.
Women can hold up half the sky.
We need
some awareness of women's rights.
Women's rights?
What's that?
It means
women should enjoy
the same rights as men.
Preposterous!
How can women be equal to men?
Your Majesty,
I believe
Princess Xiao Ling
should decide
her own marriage.
Very well.
That seems only right.
Looking good.
Keep it up.
Yes.
Two more plates of meat, please.
Coming.
Hulv!
Stop right there!
Why did you speak out in court?
What's my marriage to you?
If you've got nothing else,
quit bothering me.
I'm going to buy groceries.
How insolent!
Why didn't you kneel before me?
So what if you're a princess?
I'm a princess too.
I don't see you kneeling to me.
What's going on between you and Gu Bei?
This is for you, Miss Hulv.
Please come visit anytime.
The world doesn't belong only to men.
Women can wear armor too
and achieve greatness.
You lost
because of your brains and skills,
not because of your gender.
We started out as friends.
But
I like him.
I want to marry him.
You!
Have you no shame?
How can you say that so openly?
What's wrong with saying I like him?
I like him!
He's my prince consort!
Stay away from him.
Your prince consort?
Did he agree to that?
I can fight alongside him.
What can you do?
I have money.
I have power.
I'm beautiful.
When a steppe woman wants a man,
she gets him.
But if you can't bear to leave Gu Bei,
you can come to the plains
as our servant,
tending horses and herding sheep.
I'll fight you for this!
You're unbelievably ignorant!
Useless!
Ignorant!
Take this!
Come on!
You're so crude!
I still have memorials to review.
Forget the memorials.
We just took down General Sun.
We've got to celebrate.
Hot pot!
Your Majesty.
Gu Bei!
We beat General Sun.
Didn't I help?
Didn't I?
Of course.
Without all of you,
our plan would've never gone so smoothly.
- Then be my prince consort!
- Then marry me!
I don't think that's a good idea.
I'm still young.
It's too early to get married.
Try this.
Please.
Marry me.
I...
Marry me!
Let me say something.
- Let me speak.
- Marry me.
Now that we're all gathered here,
we've defeated the biggest villain.
So,
let's celebrate tonight.
Everyone,
drink till you drop.
- Drink till you drop!
Eat this.
Try this.
How much longer?
I need to get back to work.
On his wedding day,
Sun Beiming thought he'd already won.
But why did he prepare explosives?
Come on.
The man's dead.
Why dwell on it?
That night,
there was another signal flare.
Someone had to be sending him a message.
I think
he had someone backing him.
Drink while you can,
live for today.
Enjoy today's blessings
while they last.
Tomorrow's problems
can wait till tomorrow.
Until we find the mastermind,
we'll never know peace.
We'll always be on edge.
I think Xiaoyao Pavilion
needs an upgrade.
Great minds think alike.
I'm planning
to install surveillance.
Surveillance?
No way.
This...
Isn't this
"The Night Revels of Han Xizai"?
Bei,
you're a genius.
I don't know
whoever that Han is.
Those two work as a pair.
One sketches everything that happens,
and the other
records
every word.
From then on,
we can monitor the officials' every move
and expose the mastermind.
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Our spirit soars to the skies♪
♪The brainy emperor plots the strategy♪
♪The slacker general leads the charge♪
♪Swords clash and warhorses thunder♪
♪Let the history judge our deeds♪
♪Our brotherhood is priceless♪
♪Peace across the land, carefree at last♪
♪Funny moments never stop♪
♪Silly blunders never cease♪
♪Yet through every up and down♪
♪We create miracles♪
♪From naive youths♪
♪To legendary heroes♪
♪This journey♪
♪Is one we'll be proud of♪
♪Let's time-travel, bro♪
♪Let's create♪
♪A legend of our own♪